<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Viboo</string>
    <string name="community_guidelines">
    <![CDATA[
    <b><font color="#4CAF50"><big>Viboo Community Code</big></font></b><br><br>
    <font color="#333333" style="font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 16sp; line-height: 1.6;">
        Welcome to Viboo, a platform designed to connect people through video chats.
        To maintain a safe and enjoyable experience for all users, we ask that you follow our community guidelines.<br><br>

    <b><font color="#2196F3">1. Age Requirement</font></b><br>
    <font color="#333333">
        Users must be 18 years or older to use Viboo.
        Accounts found violating this rule will be permanently suspended.<br><br>

    <b><font color="#2196F3">2. Respectful Behavior</font></b><br>
    <font color="#333333">
        Treat others with kindness and respect during video chats.
        Bullying, harassment, hate speech, discrimination, and explicit content are strictly prohibited.<br><br>

    <b><font color="#2196F3">3. No Nudity or Sexual Content</font></b><br>
    <font color="#333333">
        Nudity, sexual acts, or sexually suggestive behavior are not allowed.
        Accounts engaging in such activities will be banned immediately.<br><br>

    <b><font color="#2196F3">4. No Illegal Activities</font></b><br>
    <font color="#333333">
        Illegal behavior, violence, or promoting illegal content is not allowed.
        This includes the use of drugs, weapons, or any activity that can cause harm.<br><br>

    <b><font color="#2196F3">5. Protect Your Privacy</font></b><br>
    <font color="#333333">
        Do not share personal information, such as phone numbers, addresses, or financial details,
        during video chats.<br><br>

    <b><font color="#2196F3">6. No Spam or Scams</font></b><br>
    <font color="#333333">
        Spamming or advertising of any kind is strictly prohibited.
        Users found engaging in scams or fraudulent activity will be banned.<br><br>

    <b><font color="#2196F3">7. Reporting Violations</font></b><br>
    <font color="#333333">
        Use the Report button to report any inappropriate behavior.
        Our moderation team will review all reports and take appropriate action.<br><br>

    <b><font color="#FF5722">Consequences for Violations</font></b><br>
    <font color="#333333">
        Breaking any of the above rules may result in temporary suspension or permanent ban of your account.
    </font>
    ]]>
</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service">
    <![CDATA[
    <b><font color="#4CAF50"><big>Viboo Terms of Use</big></font></b><br><br>
    <font color="#333333" style="font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 16sp; line-height: 1.6;">
        <b><font color="#2196F3">Effective Date:</font></b> January 5, 2025<br><br>

        Welcome to Viboo! By using our app, you agree to comply with the following terms and conditions. Please read them carefully before signing up.<br><br>

        <b><font color="#2196F3">1. Eligibility</font></b><br>
        <font color="#333333">You must be 18 years or older to create an account on Viboo.
        By signing up, you confirm that you meet the age requirement.<br><br>

        <b><font color="#2196F3">2. User Responsibilities</font></b><br>
        <font color="#333333">You are responsible for all activity on your account.
        You agree to use the app for legal purposes and to comply with all applicable laws.<br><br>

        <b><font color="#2196F3">3. Account Termination</font></b><br>
        <font color="#333333">Viboo reserves the right to suspend or terminate your account if you violate our terms or guidelines.<br><br>

        <b><font color="#2196F3">4. Paid Plans and Ads</font></b><br>
        <font color="#333333">Viboo offers a premium subscription plan to remove ads.
        By subscribing, you agree to our payment policies and auto-renewal terms.<br><br>

        <b><font color="#2196F3">5. Privacy and Data Collection</font></b><br>
        <font color="#333333">By using Viboo, you agree to our Privacy Policy regarding the collection and use of your data.<br><br>

        <b><font color="#2196F3">6. Limitation of Liability</font></b><br>
        <font color="#333333">Viboo is not responsible for any offensive or inappropriate content shared by users.
        We strive to moderate the platform but cannot guarantee a completely safe experience.<br><br>

        <b><font color="#2196F3">7. Changes to Terms</font></b><br>
        <font color="#333333">We may update these terms from time to time.
        Continued use of the app after changes means you accept the updated terms.<br><br>
    </font>
    ]]>
</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">
    <![CDATA[
    <b><font color="#4CAF50"><big>Viboo Privacy Notice</big></font></b><br><br>
    <font color="#333333" style="font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 16sp; line-height: 1.6;">
        <b><font color="#2196F3">Effective Date:</font></b> January 5, 2025<br><br>

        At Viboo, we are committed to protecting your privacy and ensuring that your data is handled securely.<br><br>

        <b><font color="#2196F3">1. Information We Collect</font></b><br>
        <font color="#333333">
            <b>Account Information:</b> Username, email address, and date of birth.<br>
            <b>Usage Data:</b> How you interact with the app, including video chat duration, ads viewed, and interactions.<br>
            <b>Device Information:</b> Device type, operating system, and IP address.<br><br>
        </font>

        <b><font color="#2196F3">2. How We Use Your Information</font></b><br>
        <font color="#333333">
            To provide and improve our services.<br>
            To display personalized ads unless you have subscribed to the ad-free plan.<br>
            To moderate content and ensure the safety of our users.<br><br>
        </font>

        <b><font color="#2196F3">3. Sharing Your Information</font></b><br>
        <font color="#333333">
            We do not share your personal information with third parties, except:<br><br>
            <font color="#333333">
                <b>To comply with legal obligations.</b><br>
                <b>To prevent fraud or illegal activities.</b><br><br>
            </font>
        </font>

        <b><font color="#2196F3">4. Your Rights</font></b><br>
        <font color="#333333">
            You have the right to access, modify, or delete your personal data. 
            You can request to delete your account at any time by contacting our support team.<br><br>
        </font>

        <b><font color="#2196F3">5. Data Security</font></b><br>
        <font color="#333333">
            We take reasonable measures to protect your data from unauthorized access. 
            However, no method of transmission over the Internet is 100% secure.<br><br>
        </font>

        <b><font color="#2196F3">6. Cookies and Tracking</font></b><br>
        <font color="#333333">
            Viboo uses cookies to enhance your experience and provide personalized ads. 
            You can manage your cookie preferences in your device settings.<br><br>
        </font>

        <b><font color="#2196F3">7. Changes to Privacy Policy</font></b><br>
        <font color="#333333">
            We may update this policy from time to time. 
            Continued use of Viboo after changes means you accept the updated policy.<br><br>
        </font>
    </font>
    ]]>
</string>


</resources>